Stacy Woodward

Epping, ND 58843 stacywoodward32_jma@indeedemail.com 701-570-9843

Accomplished Accounting professional with experience in fiscal operations, business administration, A/P, A/R, month / year-end closing, and development and implementation of procedures and policies. Experience in budgeting, financial auditing, payroll, employee taxes, and quarterly / annual company taxes. Proficient in QuickBooks and Microsoft Office.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Operations Manager

DYPEX, INC

May 2018 to Present

Accounts payable and receivable, purchasing, ordering, inventory, human resources, invoicing, reconciling credit card statements, monthly sales tax, customer service, QuickBooks, banking-deposits, remote deposit and payroll, create forms, letters, and projects as need. Creating new vendor opportunities. Also help in warehouse as needed which includes doing chemical pour-offs, cleaning, and packaging, scheduling and tracking shipments.

Owner

WOODWARD KENNELS, LLC March 2011 to Present

Boarding - clean kennels, handle dogs, assist customers, record payments, schedule customers Gun Dog Training - advertising, assisting customers, contracts, daily care, trainer, photographer Breeding/selling German Short haired Pointers, website maintenance, create contracts

City Clerk

CITY OF EPPING

January 2015 to May 2018

City Clerk, payroll and reports, minutes and meetings, meeting with public officials, answering inquiries from the general public, accounts payable and accounts receivable, county taxes, reconciling bank, QuickBooks.

Office Clerk

SCENIC SPORTS

November 2014 to November 2015

Receiving, ordering, cashier work, inventory, stocking, supervision of the cashiers, updating human resources.

Office Manager

NOVEREMBER

2010 to November 2014

FOUND IT NOW, INC

Accounts payable and receivable, purchasing, ordering, inventory, human resources, invoicing, take payment, reconciling bank and credit card statements, taxes-monthly, quarterly, yearly, and employee, customer service, QuickBooks, ADP, banking - deposits, loan payments, remote deposit and payroll, create forms, letters, and projects as need.

Education

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE in ACCOUNTING

DICKINSON STATE UNIVERSITY - Dickinson, ND August 2019 to Present

ASSOCIATES in APPLIED SCIENCE

NATIONAL AMERICAN UNIVERSITY - Rapid City, SD May 2007

Skills

- Invoicing
- Payroll and reporting and Human Resources
- ADP/Ariba/Supplier Gateway/Taulia Systems
- Accounts Receivable/Accounts Payable
- QuickBooks/Microsoft Office
- Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Office
- Inventory
- Management
- Dog Handling
- Purchasing
- · Dog Training
- Animal Care

Assessments

Accounting Skills: Bookkeeping — Highly Proficient

March 2020

Calculating and determining the accuracy of financial data.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share_to_profile/8ccc1f7ffd2a3cd0520c7191468a40e4eed53dc074545cb7

Administrative Support — Proficient

March 2020

Using basic scheduling and organizational skills in an office setting.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/attempts/cd6d409c4c23a49199a592c51fc63476eed53dc074545cb7

Administrative Support Professional Fit — Proficient

March 2020

Measures the traits that are important for successful administrative support professionals.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/attempts/d63a0a860b8d4992ea20c910f4d17e4feed53dc074545cb7

Administrative Assistant — Expert

August 2019

Using basic scheduling, attention to detail, and organizational skills in an office setting.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share to profile/

b470031c9a4bd54acbb62a57d587ef29eed53dc074545cb7

Intermediate Word Processing with Microsoft Word — Highly Proficient

July 2019

Intermediate Word techniques, including the use of formatting, Track Changes, and Comments.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/ share to profile/7b177d7a8870ad16b9031cdf0531b2cb

Management & Leadership Skills: Impact & Influence — Proficient

July 2019

Adapting leadership style to accomplish goals using rational or emotional appeal.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share_to_profile/

f16999953d5b5ce774aa092c02de1a6deed53dc074545cb7

Logic & Critical Thinking — Proficient

July 2019

Using logic to solve problems.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share to profile/

ff39d753c1c76cf7928ebd2674e7e06beed53dc074545cb7

Office Manager — Highly Proficient

July 2019

Scheduling and budgeting.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/ share to profile/9508c432924960411e707fcfdfefd852

Accounting Skills: Bookkeeping — Proficient

May 2019

Calculating and determining the accuracy of financial data.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share_to_profile/

c1ff54348b84b282fbcd27b73feedd4ceed53dc074545cb7

Management & Leadership Skills: Planning & Execution — Expert

June 2019

Planning and managing resources to accomplish organizational goals.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share to profile/0ac1c613a303803ef4b60c3474c8f0dfeed53dc074545cb7

Customer Focus & Orientation — Highly Proficient

May 2019

Responding to customer situations with sensitivity. Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share to profile/567c534145f83752810cb9cf270be62deed53dc074545cb7

Data Entry — **Expert**

May 2019

Measures a candidate's ability to accurately input data and effectively manage databases.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share to profile/47aba7a91bd7cebee4410340807bc060eed53dc074545cb7

Spreadsheets with Microsoft Excel — Proficient

May 2019

Measures a candidate's Microsoft Excel knowledge including common tools, PivotTables, conditional & nested formulas, and custom visuals.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share to profile/

f1db10bcec21a5394e2cc8736f8adaa3eed53dc074545cb7

Office Assistant — Proficient

May 2019

Cross-referencing agendas and itineraries to avoid scheduling conflicts.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share to profile/1d29b8eccb0db0737122ebc3c4c1ad7deed53dc074545cb7

Verbal Communication — **Expert**

May 2019

Measure a candidate's ability to effectively convey information when speaking.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

attempts/66114ad79031f4a3e46af0fb59e7b7eaeed53dc074545cb7

Written Communication — Proficient

May 2019

Measures a candidate's ability to convey written information using proper grammar rules.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/attempts/c7d7860f45bdd6f6023f20207d7ec8a2eed53dc074545cb7

Principles of Accounting — Highly Proficient

April 2020

Preparing financial records according to federal policies.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

attempts/31284eb111df8b384ad908cbdfe598bceed53dc074545cb7

Attention to Detail — Highly Proficient

April 2020

Identifying differences in materials, following instructions, and detecting details among distracting information.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/ attempts/17e3bed513c7d4a74240c7227abc5bd5eed53dc074545cb7

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.